thesocialmediaguide.com.au 2018-08-12

# Data Use Policy | The Social Media Guide

Collecting and Using Your Information

Thesocialmediaguide.com.au does not store any personal information. We may ask you for personal information (such as your name, or email address), but this used only to generate your privacy policy. This site does not use any database or other form of persistent storage to preserve the information you enter.

In the normal course of the site’s operation, Thesocialmediaguide.com.au generates server side logs. These are used only to monitor the performance of the application and troubleshoot errors.

Through your registration for an account at forums.Thesocialmediaguide.com.au, we may collect information you provide, as well as through placement of cookies or other tracking software on your computer to allow us to provide better service to you and our other customers.

Specifically, when you sign up for an account at forums.Thesocialmediaguide.com.au, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, address, email address and an account password). When you visit forums.Thesocialmediaguide.com.au, we may place one or more cookies on your computer to uniquely identify your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people use the forums. You may chose to set your computer to not accept cookies but some forum features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. In addition, we may track your usage of our site, communications sent to us or use of linked or related sites pertaining to our services.

Sharing of Your Information

Thesocialmediaguide.com.au will never share any information provided by its users to any third party, except as required to do so under U.S Law.

Security Pertaining to Your Information

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

Integrity of Your Data

Thesocialmediaguide.com.au processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy. We review our data collection, and processing practices to ensure that we only collect and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

Changes to this policy

Please note that we may change this Privacy Policy at various times. We expect most such changes will be minor, but we cannot guarantee that will be the case. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, if we deem it appropriate, email notification of Policy changes).

If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this Website or at Privacy Policy Concerns Coordinator
